{
    "id": "c9d638f9a5b54c47a374240c8eb47a34",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have a son and a daughter. …………… of them are good at maths.",
            "description": "We use both to talk about two people or things. All and every are used to talk about more than two people or things. ",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Both",
                "Everyone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t get there without ……………",
            "description": "Singular countable nouns take an article or another determiner with them.",
            "answers": [
                "car",
                "a car",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do with ……………. I lent you?",
            "description": "We use ‘the’ when we say which one we mean.",
            "answers": [
                "camera",
                "the camera",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you like …………..?",
            "description": "No article is used with a plural noun when we are talking about things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "dogs",
                "the dogs",
                "a dog"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked me to do the homework ……………",
            "description": "In American English, over and again are both possible here. In British English, only again is used.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "again",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "We have lived …………… this street for ten years.",
            "description": "In American English, on is used here whereas in British English, in is used.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am proud to be ………… the national football team.",
            "description": "In American English, on is used here in British English, in is used here.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "One should love …………… neighbors.",
            "description": "In British English, one’s is required whereas in American English, ‘his’ is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "one's",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that she ……………",
            "description": "We have used a special structure called the subjunctive here. In British English, the subjunctive is unusual and the structure with should + infinitive is used instead.",
            "answers": [
                "be told",
                "should be told",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never really …………… to know him.",
            "description": "In American English, the past participle of get is gotten. In British English, the past participle of get is got.",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "gotten",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds have …………….. south for the winter.",
            "description": "Flown is the past participle form of fly. To fly is to move in the air.",
            "answers": [
                "flowed",
                "flew",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………….. down and closed my eyes.",
            "description": "Lay is the past tense of lie. To lie is to ‘be down’.",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}